Wes Mora

Salt Lake City, UT 84102 | 801-674-5000 | wesmora@gmail.com

Summary

Passionate Media and Content Producer with 5+ years of experience in social media and web content creation. seeking to increase visibility within digital platforms. By working in a fast paced, deadline-driven environment. Creating new strategies that increase reach for clients.

Technical Skills

• Adobe Premiere

Wordpress

Photoshop

Spreaker

Final Cut ProAdobe Audition

• Scott Studios

• vCreative

A 1 ...

MS-Office Suite

Audacity

• Pro Tools

• Voxpro

• HTML

• CSS

• JavaScript

• MySql

Experience

CONTENT PRODUCER, ON-AIR HOST & TRAFFIC| BROADWAY MEDIA | FEB 2015 - DEC 2018

- Wrote stories, shot & edited footage, managed online web content as well as social media content.
- Hosted and produced a daily radio program talking about pop culture, local stories, and life.
- Coordinated, planned and conducted live interviews with local leadership and community personnel.
- Maintained deadlines to provide timely traffic updates on KEGA, KYMV, and KUUU during AM commute.

AUDIO ENGINEER | INSTORE BROADCASTING NETWORK | MAY 2005 - DECEMBER 2014

- Applied production skills to creatively utilize all aspects of digital production to create client audio production.
- Coordinated and coached voice talent on interpretation of read for best delivery of voice over project.
- Able to work with and manage different types of personalities in the workplace.
- Adept at working in a fast-paced, deadline-oriented, collaborative environment.

PRODUCTION DIRECTOR | ALPHA MEDIA USA | OCTOBER 2015 - JUNE 2016

- Created, edited and oversaw quality-control for commercial production used on-air.
- Planned, coordinated and conducted recording sessions with various clients.
- Translated copy for account executives that did not speak Spanish and produced spots.
- Managed and loaded all syndicated programming to run on the correct cluster station.

BRAND MANAGER & PROMOTIONS DIRECTOR | iHEART MEDIA | NOV 2011 - DEC 2013

- Managed projects for 6 radio stations and ensured timelines were being met with a team of 8 to 10 people.
- Worked with sales teams to develop promotions for clients, and effectively execute marketing programs.
- Trained and managed a team of assistants regarding appropriate project assessments and protocols.
- Managed promotional calendars, including workflow coordination, talent management and broadcast equipment, as well as met regularly with programming to brainstorm ideas related to contests and events.

ON AIR NIGHTS & MORNING DRIVE | SIMMONS MEDIA | MAY 2010 - AUGUST 2011

- Hosted a nightly radio program from 7pm to midnight, and a tracked morning show.
- Created, prepared and presented up to date topics for morning and night shows with interactive calls.
- Managed, wrote and scheduled online media stories as well as social media content.
- Conducted on-air interviews and panel discussions on various topics.

Wes Mora

Salt Lake City, UT 84102 | 801-674-5000 | wesmora@gmail.com

Education

WEB DESIGN CERTIFICATE PROGRAM | FEB 2019-JUN 2019 | SALT LAKE COMMUNITY COLLEGE

In the process of completing a 23-week professional training certification course focused on the skills needed to design and build web applications. The program includes hundreds of hours of professional development and hands-on practice.

Focus:

- Adobe Photoshop Creative Cloud
- Front-End Web Development Using Photoshop, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap
- Back-end Development In PHP
- Capstone Project And Showcase
- Internship Designing For Local Business Partners

WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE PROGRAM | APRIL 2018-OCT 2018 | UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

Completed a 24-week professional training certification course focused on the skills needed to build fully responsive end to end web applications.

The program includes over 250 in class hours and 300+ out of class hours of professional development and hands-on practice.

Focus:

- Programming Fundamentals
- Product Development Basics
- Front-End Web Development(HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Bootstrap, AJAX, various JS libraries)
- Back-end Development (APIs, PHP, NODE.js, Express.js, MySQL, MongoDB)
- Database Theory
- · Command Line, Git

RADIO AND MEDIA PROGRAM | 2004-2006 | SALT LAKE COMMUNITY COLLEGE

Completed 60 credit hours towards Associates Degree in Radio And Media.